- 爸 咱得谈谈 - 谈什么 那些蜜蜂吗
- Dad, we need to talk. - Is it about the bees?
-蜜蜂 -两周后
- Bees? - We're throwing
我们准备开一个暖房派对
a housewarming party in two weeks.
哦
Oh.
朋友们啊 邻居们啊都要过来
It's gonna be friends,neighbors...
他刚才说的是 他说的是蜜蜂吗
Did he say... did he say "bees"?
是啊 马修这几天没日没夜地工作
Yeah. Marshall's been working very long hours lately,
所以我只好一个人准备这个派对
so I have been planning this whole party by myself,
所有东西都买齐了 吃的 喝的
and everything's in place: the food, the wine.
我还从网上买了一块很赞的高达奶酪
I even found a rare Gouda on the Internet.
噢
Oh.
回到蜜蜂的话题
Getting back to these bees...
不管如何 这个派对对我来说很重要
Bottom line: this party is very important to me,
所以我觉得 当然我是充满爱意说的
so I can only assume-- and I say this with love--
你肯定会把派对搞砸了
you're gonna ruin it.
莉莉 我保证不会搞砸你的派对
Lily, I promise I won't ruin your party.
我保证表现得又迷人又有爱
I'll be charming and convivial.
表现得像正常的伯特・雷诺（美国一影星）
A regular Burt Reynolds.
你真没什么需要顾虑的
You have absolutely nothing to worry about.
给我们讲讲蜜蜂的事儿
Tell us about the bees!
好吧 既然你问了
Well, all right, since you asked.
我开始做养蜂这一行了
I'm starting up a business
生产全有机的 全手工制作的蜂蜜
cultivating all-organic, artisanal honey.
没错 我在创业
That's right, I'm a job creator.
喔 那么这场派对
Oh. So this party...
噢 莉莉 等等 呃 如果你不介意的话
Oh, Lily, wait. Um, if you don't mind,
我 还有个小问题
I just, I have one follow-up.
你在哪儿做这个呢
Where are you doing this exactly?
楼下啊 地下室里有一万只蜜蜂
Downstairs-- there's 10,000 bees in the basement.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十五集
翻译:  加菲猪 47.4 Roy Andie Cathy
后期+统筹: Cathy 47.4校对: 安达小充 Henry
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
祝大家元宵节快乐
-你干嘛那样讲话 -简直太...
- Why would you even say that?! - It's the most ridic..
暖房快乐
Happy Housewarming
嘿 伙计们
Hey Guys
罗宾用了一整天的时间
Robin here has spent
鸡蛋蒸锅是类似馅饼一样的犹太人食物,一般由鸡蛋面或土豆做成,其中还放入诸多配料
学做鸡蛋蒸锅
all day learning how to make kugel.
Zabar为曼哈顿上西区知名超市
不过没学会 这是从扎巴餐厅买的
Couldn't figure it out-- this is from Zabar's.
能用你家烤箱加热下吗
Can we heat it up in your oven?
哈 用烤箱总比用冰箱加热快一些
Faster than heating it up in the refrigerator.
我喝了几杯鸡尾酒
I've had a few cocktails.
-给我吧 -拿着吧
- I got it. - Take that.
孩子们 有一天你们要办一个派对
Kids, someday you're gonna throw a party,
那时候你就会担心
and you might find yourself worrying
一些事情要出岔子
if something's gonna go wrong.
不用担心
Well, don't.
你实际要担心的是所有事情都要出岔子
What you should worry about is everything going wrong.
出事速度之快 绝对让你胆寒
And what's really scary is how quickly that can happen.
比如莉莉和马修的暖房派对
At Lily and Marshall's housewarming party
就只用了5分钟
for instance, it only took five minutes.
在这5分钟里发生了很多事
Now, a lot happened in those five minutes.
知道吗 我打算一个屋一个屋的说
You know what? I'm gonna take this room by room.
先从起居室说起
We'll start in the living room.
哦 不好 那可不行
Oh, no, that's not what you want.
- 啥 - 没事儿 你觉得
- What? - Oh, nothing. So, you think
你觉得这个派对怎么样
this is going pretty well?
宝贝 你开玩笑呢
Baby, are you kidding?
你一手操办了本年度最棒派对
You single-handedly pulled off the party of the year.
不要说了啦 人家用了两只手嘛
Oh, stop it. I used both hands.
那么 我能帮你干点什么
So, what can I do to help?
亲爱的 你好不容易才休息一次
Honey, this is your first night off in however long.
你就好好歇着 喝点小酒
You just relax and keep knocking back those cocktails.
库茨先生
Mr. Cootes.
终于能休息一晚上 感觉挺好吧
Hey, isn't it nice to finally have a night off?
是啊 但今晚轮不着咱们休息
It is. But tonight is not that night.
45分钟后我们得赶回公司
We're going back to the office in 45 minutes.
先生 可这是我们的暖房派对啊
But, sir, this is our housewarming party.
你知道么 地球母亲也正在开一个
You know, Mother Earth is also having
暖 房派对
a "housewarming" party, too,
只是她的派对是以海面上升 人类沉到海底
only hers ends with humankind at the bottom of a rising ocean,
被黄貂鱼吃进肚子告终的
passing through the digestive tract of a stingray.
不管怎样 你家真漂亮
By the way, it's a lovely home.
库茨先生 我知道您是素食主义者 所以我
Mr. Cootes, I know you're a vegan, so I, uh,
在那儿给您准备了几个素馅春卷
I got some vegan spring rolls for you over there.
噢 美味哟
Oh, nummies!
你要赶回去工作
You're going back to work?
诶哟 马修 你简直跟那啥一样忙
Sheez, Marshall, you are as busy as a...
哦 对了 你跟啥一样忙来着
Oh, gosh, what are you as busy as?
求求你别说蜜蜂
Please don't talk about the bees.
其实我想说你跟尼古拉斯・凯奇一样忙
I was gonna say Nicolas Cage.
那爷们啥都演
That guy is in everything.
咱放点音乐吧
Let's just put on some music.
我 呃 我去把高达奶酪拿出来
I'll, uh, I'll bring out the Gouda,
我们开几瓶红酒
we'll open a couple bottles of wine...
可那些红酒在地下室
that are in the basement.
好吧 我去拿养蜂人的防护服去
All right, I'll get my beekeeper's suit.
你们该因为蜜蜂高兴
You should be happy about the bees.
它们把老鼠困在了地下室
They're keeping the mice at bay.
这儿还有老鼠
We have mice?
不过蜜蜂到处飞
Not with all these bees
就没有了
flying around, we don't.
不用客气哈
You're welcome.
泰德 小高达要出来了 表现得活跃点
Ted, baby Gouda's coming out. Look alive.
你是素食主义者吗
Are you a vegan?
啥
What?
喔咿
Ooh-ee!
来厨房 现在
Kitchen, now.
我真不敢相信库茨非要我们晚上加班
I can't believe that he's making us go to work tonight.
你 是不是 一个 素食主义者
Are... you... a... vegan?
嗯 不是的
Um, no.
好的 那当你一口口地把春卷咽下去的时候
Uh-huh. And when you were shoveling
有没有注意到放春卷的盘子上
the spring rolls down your gullet, did you happen to notice
清晰地标着 素食者专用
a little sign next to the plate marked "Vegan"?
我觉着咱俩之间有点儿误会
I think there's been some mistake.
你可以吃了那桌上的任何东西
You could have had anything on that table!
任何   东西
Anything at all!
迷你披萨饼 培根卷无花果
Mini pizzas, bacon-wrapped figs,
猪肉肠面包卷
pigs in blankets.
据说甚至还有原产地的高达奶酪
There was even talk of an inbound Gouda!
但是 不 不 你居然唯独吃了那一样东西
But no, no, you had to have the one thing
像我这样的素食者唯一可以吃的东西
that someone with my dietary preferences can eat.
听着 我没有吃春卷
Look, I didn't eat the spring rolls.
骗子
Liar!
你的呼吸里都带着一丝丝胡萝卜和欺骗的恶臭
Your breath reeks of shredded carrots and deceit!
好的 好的 或许我确实吃了你的春卷
Okay, okay, maybe I did eat your precious spring rolls.
哦
Oh...
你又能把我怎么样呢 你这个小嬉皮士
What are you gonna do about it, hippie?
没事 一切顺利
It's fine. Everything's fine.
年轻人
Young man,
你是在挑衅
are you suggesting fisticuffs...
要跟我用拳头一绝高低么
as in with our fists?
不仅仅是拳头 还有脚 我腿法了得
And feet-- I'm a kicker.
好好好 这感觉就像
Well, well, looks like I just started eating
我回归食肉了那样
white meat again.
我会像一只狼灌一样撕咬你的
I will bite and scratch you like a wolverine.
让我警告你一遍
May I warn you,
我以前可打过架
I have been in a fight before.
我也打过 一丢丢
So have I... sort of.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
库茨先生 嗨
Mr. Cootes. Hi.
你看见我们那儿放了豆沙和蔬菜么
Did you see that we had hummus and veggies?
豆沙和蔬菜
There's hummus and veggies?
就在那儿
Over there.
嘿 我可不会再任人宰割了
Hey, I'm not gonna let that guy push me around.
我可坚信孙子兵法里有
I believe it was Sun Tzu who wrote, "Never give up.
永不言败 永不投降
Never surrender."
-闭嘴 泰德 -好的
-Shut up, Ted.    -Okay.
老天啊 莉莉 你可是怀孕了的
For God's sake, Lily, you're pregnant.
老天啊 泰德 莉莉可是怀孕了的
For God's sake, Ted,Lily's pregnant.
哦 天啊
Oh, man.
非常抱歉发生了这种事
Sorry about that.
我现在不需要你的抱歉 泰德
I don't need this right now, Ted.
我不该这么做的
I shouldn't do this.
-我不该这么做啊   -怎么了
- I shouldn't do this. - What?
这个主意糟透了 这个主意糟透了
This is a bad idea. This is a bad idea!
-到底怎么了 -我应该现在闪人 现在就走
- What is? - I should just go. I should just go!
好吧 好吧 告诉我到底发生了什么
Okay, okay, just tell me what is going on.
我爱我的弟弟 罗宾
I love my penis, Robin.
哦 巴尼 你承诺过的
Oh, Barney, you promised.
我是承诺过 我爱它
I do! I love it!
如果我可以亲到它的话 我会去亲的
If I could kiss it, I would.
如果我跟你说我没试过 那我一定在撒谎
I'd be lying if I told you I hadn't tried.
这话题让我感觉到不爽
I'm not comfortable with this conversation.
哦 别这样啊罗宾 我们可是在谈论我的弟弟
Oh, come on, Robin, it's my penis we're talking about.
-你曾经见过她 她是多么的神奇   -她
- You've seen her-- she's magnificent. - She?
每一个小弟弟都是个姑娘 罗宾 所有人都知道
Every penis is a girl, Robin. Everyone knows that.
就好像 水怪和船都是姑娘一样
Like... ships and lake monsters.
还有高达
And Gouda!
她很美哒
She's a beauta.
哦 高达奶酪
Oh, Gouda.
好吧 我会回来的
Well, I'll be back.
不管怎么样 我身体的大部分会回来的
Most of me, anyway.
-别吃这个 -什么
- Don't eat that.   - What?
我擦 哦 这被毁了
Whoops! Oh, it's ruined.
这没有被毁啊 落地十秒内拿起来还可以吃啊
It's not ruined. Ten second rule.
八 九 十 好了 它被毁了
Eight, nine, ten, and it's ruined.
这整个派对都被毁了
This whole party's ruined.
我的储藏室里到处都是蜜蜂
I got a basement full of bees,
而泰德差点和库茨先生打起来
and Ted almost got into a fight with Mr. Cootes.
莉莉 看看四周
Lily, look around.
每个人都在享受一段神奇的时光
Everyone's having an amazing time.
这是个很棒的派对
It's a great party.
好吧 或许这不全是一场灾难
Okay, maybe it's not a total disaster.
那是什么玩意儿
What the hell was that?!
这就是发生在客厅的事儿
So that's what happened in the living room.
现在让我们把目光转向餐厅
Now I'm gonna tell you what happened in the dining room.
哦 不好 那可不行
Oh, no, that's not what you want.
哦 难以置信这些居然是素食
Man, I can't believe these are vegan.
我吃了 将近二十个
I've had, like, 20 of 'em.
我该去问问做这个的餐馆的名字
I should get the name of this caterer.
下礼拜是我那只叫蝙蝠的小猫的成人礼
It's my kitten's Bat Mitzvah next week.
她终于真正成为了一只猫
She's finally becoming a cat.
哦 老天 你真是个疯...
Oh, God, you are crazy.
狂热爱猫的人
About cats.
猫都很忠诚而且情感真挚
Cats are so honest and real with their affections.
自从我离婚后
Ever since my divorce,
我身边的骗子就像过流水灯一样
it's just been one liar after another.
所以感觉如此新鲜当我遇到了如此诚实的你
That's why it's so refreshing to meet someone honest like you,
特工咖喱泡沫
Special Agent Gary Powers.
听着
Listen...
我觉得我们之间达成了某种联系
I think we can agree there's something here.
某种丰满的
Something big...
看上去很真实 可能感觉也会很真实的联系
that looks and probably feels real.
或许
Maybe...
我们可以去你的地方
we can go back to your place.
我可不能让你延误了去拦截那些小行星
I can't ask you to delay intercepting those asteroids.
我确实得去拦截那些行星
I do need to intercept those asteroids.
我感觉我们应该现在就去滚床单
I think we need to have sex right now.
两分钟后楼上的客房见
Meet me in the upstairs guest bedroom in two minutes.
你们知道那斋春卷在哪里吗
I'm just looking for the vegan spring rolls.
不好意思 最后一个我吃了
Last one, sorry.
两分钟后哦
Two minutes.
它们怎么就没了 派对才刚开始啊
How can they all be gone? The party just started.
可不
I know, right?
咱放点音乐吧
Let's just put on some music.
我 呃 我去把高达奶酪拿出来
I'll, uh, I'll bring out the Gouda,
我们开几瓶红酒
we'll open a couple of bottles of wine...
可那些红酒在地下室
that are in the basement.
有个混蛋刚才在这
Some jerk was just here.
他就像这样
And he was all, like,
难以置信这些居然是素食
"I can't believe these are vegan.
我吃了 将近二十个
I've had, like, 20 of 'em."
指给我看那个挨千刀的在哪儿
Point me into the direction of this scoundrel.
喏 就是那个家伙
Um... it was that guy.
泰德 小高达要出来了 表现得活跃点
Ted, baby Gouda's coming out. Look alive.
莉莉 这些春卷 喔咿
Lily, these spring rolls... ooh-ee!
来厨房 现在
Kitchen, now.
我真不敢相信库茨非要我们晚上加班
I can't believe that he's making us go to work tonight.
我就是觉得现在得有人把他拉到一个安静点的地方
I mean, I think it's time that somebody took him aside
然后告诉他这么摧残自己的手下是会遭报应的
and told him this is not how you treat your staff.
唔 我现在忙的都脱不开身了
Well, I'm sort of busy with the party right now.
好吧 还得我自己来 不过他会朝我大喊大叫的
Fine. I'll do it myself. But he's gonna scream at me,
而你知道我最受不了别人吵我大喊大叫了
and you know that I can't stand up to screaming.
-去和他谈谈 -我也觉得应该和他好好谈谈了
- Just go talk to him! - I think I should go talk to him.
-巴尼 -哦 莉莉
- Barney... - Ah, Lily,
春卷都被泰德一人吃光了
Ted ate all of the spring rolls.
你可以吃了那桌上的任何东西
You could have had anything on that table!
迷你匹萨饼 培根卷无花果
Mini pizzas, bacon-wrapped figs,
猪肉肠面包卷
pigs in blankets.
据说甚至还有原产地的高达奶酪
There was even talk of an inbound Gouda!
罗宾 嗯 听着 我需要你帮我一下
Robin. Okay, listen, I need your help.
我马上就要和我的老板来一个对骂比赛了
I'm about to get in a screaming match with my boss,
而且我又不擅长被别人大喊大叫
and I'm not good at getting screamed at,
所以我需要你帮我热身
so I need you to warm me up.
-怎么热身 -我要你使劲骂我
- How? - I want you to scream at me.
对 就像你被街边的路人甲以一点点小事激怒那样
You know, like you do to strangers on the street
对我开炮吧
at the slightest provocation.
我从来没有过好吧
I don't do that.
来吗 给我点经典的贱人舍巴斯基
Come on, lay some of that classic Scherbatsky
向我开炮吧
mean son of a bitch on me.
就像那些小童子军向你叫卖曲奇那样对我吧
Treat me like I'm a Girl Scout trying to sell you cookies.
四美元一盒 你穷疯了是吗
Four dollars a box and you're out of Thin Mints?!
你个小绿…… 我不这样的
You green little...! I don't do that!
麻利点 对我大吼大叫吧
Come on, scream at me.
就像那样
Like that.
没事 一切顺利
It's fine. Everything's fine.
马修 有很多事情
Marshall, there is plenty of stuff
都激怒不了我的
that I don't get mad about,
比如你在准备这些猪肉肠面包卷的时候
like the fact that you're serving pigs in blankets
居然没准备芥末
without hot mustard.
我可不是那种人 那种就只为这宴会东家连上这道
I'm not the type of person to be driven crazy by a host
猪肉肠面包卷的时候连芥末都不准备
who refuses to provide delicious hot mustard
就立马火冒三丈的人
in which to dip my pigs in blankets!
我是那种 让自己冷静下来的妹子
I'm the type of girl who... keeps her cool.
让自己冷静下来的那种
Who keeps her cool.
等下 哇哦 亲爱的 你没事吧
Wait. Whoa, baby, are you okay?
当然没事了 这派对多好啊
Of course. This party is great.
一切尽在掌握 哦 天呐
I am handling this. Oh, God.
别
No...
豆泥加蔬菜呢
Hummus and veggies?
豆泥和蔬菜在哪里啊
I'm looking for hummus and veggies.
罗宾 我能和你讨论一件对我来说很珍贵的东西吗
Robin, can I talk to you about something very dear to me?
你发誓和你的小弟弟无关
Promise me this isn't about your penis.
我保证这绝对和我的小弟弟无关
I promise it isn't about my penis.
不好意思啊
I'm sorry.
不好意思 头儿 我能和你到厨房说两句话吗
Excuse me, sir, could I talk to you in the kitchen?
实在抱歉啊
Sorry about that.
我现在不需要你的抱歉 泰德
I don't need this right now, Ted.
我发誓 要是哪里再出点什么乱子
I swear, if there's one more crisis...
好吧 这些蜜蜂都跑出来了
Well, the bees escaped their enclosure,
但这点小事情犯不着大家蜂蜂颠颠的
but no reason to "Bee" Concerned.
好吧 我确实惹麻烦了
No, there is, we're in big trouble.
你那是什么味道
What is that smell?
我把我的外套放在煤油里泡了一会儿
Oh, I doused my suit with kerosene.
所有的养蜂人都这么干
All beekeepers do this.
老爸 现在就把这外衣脱了
Dad, just take off the suit right now.
好吧
All right, fine.
每30秒
Every 30 seconds,
就有一个新的麻烦等着去解决
there's another crisis that needs to be dealt with
而且还必须得是我去解决
and I have to deal with it.
简直是 哦天呐
This is... Oh, God.
当爹妈就是这样吧 是不是
This is parenthood, isn't it?
过来人都这么说
So they say.
好吧 我正式宣布
Okay, it's official.
我以为我可以做到 但是我做不到
I thought I could do it, but I can't.
我做不到 马修永远都在工作
No, Marshall's always at work.
他今天晚上就得再回去了
He's got to go back tonight.
而且我实在是不知道我道理能不能处理好
And I don't know if I can handle a life
这一波接着一波混乱的人生啊
that's just one crisis after another.
莉莉 听好了 我要给你一点小
Lily, listen to me. I'm gonna give you a little piece of...
高达
Gouda!
天呐
God.
-又有麻烦了吗 -又有麻烦了
- Crisis? - Crisis.
-别吃那个 呦 -什么
- Don't eat that. Whoops! - What?
高达出场了 泰德 别在上面吃睡着了
Gouda's out, Ted. Don't sleep on the Gouda.
我可不想
Wouldn't dream of it.
那么莉莉告诉我说你今晚得回去工作是吧
So Lily told me you have to go back to work tonight?
不 我今晚不用回去工作了
No, I don't have to go back to work tonight.
库茨先生和我达成了共识
Mr. Cootes and I came to an understanding.
但是 嘿 罗宾怎么了
But, hey, what's going on with Robin?
我说她是个自私的婊子
I called her a mean son of a bitch
然后她的反应太奇怪了
and she took it all weird.
-很奇怪吗   -是的
- She did? - Yeah.
不正常 对吧
Crazy, right?
嘿 大伙儿
Hey, buddy.
史上最棒的暖房派对
Best housewarming party ever.
每个人都嗡嗡的
Everybody's abuzz.
嗡嗡的
Abuzz.
噢 一语双关 米奇
Oh, good one, Mickey.
但是 嘿 你说的很对
But, hey, you're right.
很棒的派对
Great party.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell was that?!
这就是发生在餐厅的事情
And that's what happened in the dining room.
现在我要告诉你们在厨房发生了什么
Now I'm gonna tell you what happened in the kitchen.
哦 不好 那可不行
Oh, no, that's not what you want.
哦 难以置信这些居然是素食
Man, I can't believe these are vegan.
回到争吵状态
Back to our fight?
Back to our fight.
我不敢相信你在扎吧对一个女人大喊大叫
I cannot believe you screamed at that woman at Zabar's.
她想要插队
She was trying to cut in line.
她想要拿走最后一份鸡蛋蒸锅
She was gonna get the last kugel.
她已经90高龄了
She was 90 years old.
这可能也是她的最后一份鸡蛋蒸锅了
It was probably gonna be her last kugel.
有些时候 你需要果断一点
Sometimes in life, you have to be assertive
保护自己利益
and stand up for yourself.
你管叫她婊子
You called her a whore.
谁没事化这么浓的妆
Who wears that much makeup?!
老婆婆们
Old ladies!
那些卖身换钱的人 太对了
Who take money for sex. Exactly.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
如果我把这件事情交给你那白皙秀丽
If I would've left things in your dainty, lily-white,
从未薅掉一个老婆婆假发的手里
never-ripped- an-old-lady's-wig-off hands,
我们现在就没有鸡蛋蒸锅了
we would be kugel-free right now.
哦 所以说呢 我太好了
Oh, so, what, I'm too nice?
你从来不为自己争取
You never stand up for yourself.
记得那个一直偷你午饭的六年级生么
Remember that sixth grader who kept stealing your lunch?
高中是我的艰难时代 好么
High school was a tough time for me, okay?
而且那个女孩是肌肉型的
And that girl was muscular.
手臂跟大力水手一样
Forearms like Popeye.
你怎么会知道这件事的
How do you even know about that?
马修告诉我的 他还说了
Marshall told me. He also said that
你让你妈妈不再做
you had your mom stop making
果酱和花生酱三明治
peanut butter and jelly sandwiches
因为那个女孩对坚果过敏
because of that girl's nut allergy.
我不想加重她的身体问题
I didn't want to add to her health problems.
她已经坐轮椅了
She was already in a wheelchair.
好的 所以呢
Okay, so what?
我宁愿忍让些也不愿做你这样的人
I would rather be nice than be like you,
总是跟人争执那些
always getting in fights about stuff
鸡毛蒜皮不值得的小事
that's not even worth fighting about.
不同意
Disagree.
孙子在孙子兵法里面写过
It's like Sun Tzu wrote in The Art of War,
永不言败 永不投降
"Never give up. Never surrender."
那是提姆艾伦在星河奇遇里面写的
That was Tim Allen in Galaxy Quest.
无论如何 哥们
Whatever, dude.
你的问题就是无论何时
Your problem is any time you're faced with
面对任何对峙的时候 你就逃跑
the least bit of confrontation, you run away.
哦 我在逃避对峙
Oh, I run away from confrontation?
泰德 小高达要出来了
Ted, baby Gouda's coming out.
表现得活跃点
Look alive.
哦 你个...
Whoops. Son of a...!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
也许那是我的错
Maybe that was my fault.
你也发现了
You think?
你挡住了我拿吃的的路
You're right in my snack track.
嘿 帅气的养蜂人装束
Hey, nice beekeeper suit.
你知道么 大多数蜜蜂是左撇子
Do you know that, uh, most bees are left-handed?
你知道蜜蜂很讨厌煤油的味道么
Did you know bees hate the smell of kerosene?
我当然知道 天呐 你以为
I knew that. Geez, what do you think,
这是我当养蜂人的第一天么
this is my first day as a beekeeper?
太棒了 哦
Nice. Oh.
蜜蜂讨厌煤油是真的么
Is that true about bees and kerosene?
我不知道
I don't know.
巴尼
Barney...
哦 莉莉
Ah, Lily,
春卷都被泰德一人吃光了
Ted ate all of the spring rolls.
巴尼 那个跟你说话的女人
Barney, that woman you were talking to,
也就是我们的邻居杰拉德琳
our neighbor Geraldine,
有个人跟她睡了
some guy slept with her
却没再打电话给她 于是她追踪到了他
and didn't call her, so she hunted him down
然后用一把芝士刀切掉了他身体的某个部分
and cut off a certain part of his anatomy with a cheese knife.
所以 无论你做什么
So, whatever you do,
别上她
don't sleep with her.
这太有趣了 她在 唔
It's funny, she is, um, waiting for me
她正在客卧等着我
in the guest bedroom right now.
哦 天呐 哦 天呐
Oh, God! Oh, God!
那是原本的打算 但是我现在已经忘了
That was the idea, but now forget it!
巴尼 这是一场灾难
Barney, this is a disaster.
我发誓 只要这里有一个..
I swear, if there is one...
没事 一切顺利
It's fine. Everything's fine.
十秒法则:掉在地上的东西十秒内捡起来都是干净的
嘿 不超过十秒 对吧
Hey, ten second rule, right?
没事 一切顺利
It's fine. Everything's fine.
走开 走开 走开
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
我知道你怀孕了 但你需要来点酒压压惊
I know you're pregnant, but you need a glass of wine.
这块奶酪我是从网上买的
I got that cheese off the Internet.
我知道你是在网上买的
I know you got it off the Internet.
网上买的又咋了
Why does that make it impressive?
你知道网上还有什么吗
You know what else you can find on the Internet?
动物园里的动物打飞机
Zoo animals masturbating.
哥还见过一只海象
There's one of a walrus.
他
He's...
噢
Oh.
别
No...
不好意思 头儿 我能和你到厨房说两句话吗
Excuse me, sir, could I talk to you in the kitchen?
库茨先生 今晚我是不会回去工作的
Mr. Cootes, I am not going back to work tonight.
喔 她刚刚说了什么
Oh, no, she didn't just say that.
米奇 能给我们俩一会儿时间单独谈谈
Mickey, could we just have a minute?
哦 好的 当然可以
Oh, yeah. Sure.
马修 你看 我知道当你刚来公司的时候
Marshall, look, I know when you started with this firm,
我们的工作看起来很有意思
it was all fun and games.
尤其是晋升大战更激动人心
The office chair races were particularly spirited.
直到 呃 盖尔从楼梯上摔了下去
Until, of course, Gail went down the stairs.
但就在那个瞬间
But for one brief moment,
神哪 我相信她飞起来了
boy, did she fly.
当我没在 当我没在
I'm not here, I'm not here.
库茨先生 你是个极品工作狂
Mr. Cootes, you're working yourself to death.
拜托就放松那么一会儿
Just cut loose a little.
来点啤酒 发展发展兴趣爱好
Have a beer, find a hobby.
你看 孩子 道理很简单
Look, son, it's very simple.
嗯 地球母亲从来都不休息
Um, Mother Earth doesn't get a night off.
所以你也休想
Neither do you.
那好 我辞职
Well, then I quit.
我真不知道我能不能去适应这种生活
And I don't know if I can handle a life
烦心事一件接一件的发生
that's just one crisis after another.
莉莉 听好了 我要给你一点小
Lily, listen to me. I'm gonna give you a little piece of...
高达
Gouda!
他可能是对的
Maybe he's right.
我或许确实需要培养一个兴趣爱好
Maybe I do need a hobby.
呃 嘿 养蜜蜂怎么样
Well, hey, how about beekeeping?
我 不好 关于蜜蜂我是什么都不知道
Me? No. I-I don't know the first thing about bees.
告诉你个秘密
You want to know a secret?
我也不懂
Neither do I.
这个不是秘密
It's not a secret.
我试试这件装备
Let me try this thing on.
那我回避一下
I'm gonna give you some privacy.
好的 谢谢
All right, thank you.
好
Okay.
嘿 哥们
Hey, buddy.
史上最棒的暖房派对
Best housewarming party ever.
每个人都嗡嗡的
Everybody's abuzz.
好吧 貌似没想象中的那么糟
Okay, maybe it's not a total disaster.
很棒的派对
Great party.
喔 天啊 噢
Oh, my God. Oh!
噢 库茨先生
Oh, Mr. Cootes!
库茨先生 您还好吧
Mr. Cootes, are you okay?!
爽死了
That was amazing!
你看见没
Did you see me?!
我像个人肉火球一样飞过来
I flew through the air like a human fireball
而且居然毫发无损
and didn't get a scratch.
羡慕不死你 盖尔
Eat your heart out, Gail!
老天爷 我浑身充满活力
God, I feel so alive!
我想喝点啤酒
I want to drink a beer.
哦 好的
Oh, yeah.
没问题 啤酒一瓶 即可送上
Okay, one beer, coming right up.
哦 等等 马修
Oh, and, uh, Marshall,
我想今天晚上我们都放个假 好不
I think we'll take the night off tonight, okay?
听起来不错 好的
Sounds good, yeah.
但礼拜一你来上班吧
But I'll see you Monday?
那是当然的
Of course.
说定了
Yeah.
你知道么 罗宾 我一直在想
You know, Robin, I've been thinking about it.
你牌鹄匆猜好的
Guess it's kind of nice you're such a badass.
你好起来也蛮诺 泰德
It's pretty badass you're so nice, Ted.
我是不是应该把地下室的门关上
Was I supposed to close the basement door?
天啊 感觉太好了
God, this feels so right!
咱俩太登对了
We're so great together.
我想在你身边而且寸步不离
I want to spend every minute of every day with you.
我要时刻监视着你
I never let you out of my sight for one second.
连一秒也不要让你离开我的世界
Not one second, not one second. I don't!
噢 天啊
Oh, God!
我的上一个可没这么好
My last lover was not like this.
他最烂了
He was the worst!
你知道么 他都不来参加我猫猫的割礼
Do you know, he didn't even come to my cat's bris.
我说 什么
I mean, what?
所以我就让他亲身体验了下
Well, we showed him.
没错 我们真这么干了
Yes, we did.
可以这么说 我们量刑得当
Let's just say, the punishment fit the crime.
我都迫不及待要告诉所有的人
I can't wait to tell everybody
我们俩是一对儿了
that we're boyfriend and girlfriend!
今晚就宣布吧
Let's do it tonight.
算了 这是莉莉和马修的派对
No, it's Lily and Marshall's party.
再等等吧
We'll wait.
我们等到羊肉小姐和呼叫先生的婚礼上再说吧
We can do it at Mittens and Mr. Pepper's wedding.
或者
Or maybe something...